#### **PROFILE**

Experienced researcher, leader, and salesman with passion to be a part of cutting-edge software design. Key skills include communication, research, software development, various MS Office product, and problem solving. Experiences include two different research studies at WVU, sales associate position and continued leadership studies as a cadet in Army ROTC.

"Jackman clearly has the potential to serve as a Commissioned officer and leader" – CPT Patrick Angus 11<sup>th</sup> ADA Brigade 343D Commander

# QUALIFICATIONS & DESIGNATIONS



- Secret clearance
- Eagle Scout
- Sam Houston Council BSA Top District Salesman – 3 years

### **CONTACT INFO**

PHONE: 713-851-9117 EMAIL: Jtj0002@mix.wvu.edu

#### **REFERENCES**

Christopher Voss: 540-454-8868 Christopher.j.voss5.mil@mail.mil Matthew Shraeder: 304-293-5322 mrschraeder@mix.wvu.edu Patrick Angus: 915-892-5480 Patrick.b.angus.mil@mail.mil

# JAMES T. JACKMAN

Phone: 713-851-9117 Email: <u>itj0002@mix.wvu.edu</u> Address: 911 Domain Dr. Morgantown WV, 26501

Software Engineer Intern

### **EDUCATION**

### **West Virginia University**

Aug 2016 - present

Expected Graduation: Dec 2020

GPA: 3.42 Major: Computer Science
Senior cadet for US Army ROTC
Participated in two research studies

Clear Falls High School AUG 2012 – JUN 2016

**GPA**: 3.46

### **WORK EXPERIENCE & RESEARCH**

#### **US Army ROTC - Officer in Training**

Aug 2016 - Present

- Selected to be a part of month-long cadet internship during FY19
  - Key player in maintaining a positive command climate throughout the battery.
  - Planed a multi domain training exercise involving multimillion-dollars' worth of equipment.
  - Recommended by commanding officer for leading twohour tactical convoy integrating all aspects of tactical communication.
- Mentored and reinforced proper conduct for junior cadets when interactives with senior officers.
- Orchestrated sale and distribution of Big 12 WVU Football programs. Trained/managed 30 cadets in the distribution of programs. Team achieved overall top sales position.

# **Bay Area Trees & Landscaping – Customer Service / Sales Associate**May 2018 – Aug 2018

- Helped customers with questions concerning landscaping and aardenina.
- Cross trained and provided backup for other customer service representatives when needed.
- Balanced daily cash drawer.

# **Lane Department of Computer Science – Undergrad Researcher** Aug 2016 – Dec 2017

- Participated in EEG readings research with Dr. Van Scoy.
  - Produced EEG reading data using Microsoft excel.
- Participated in big data research with Dr. Savage.
  - Created graphical representations of big data using Microsoft excel.

#### **SKILLS**

- Effective communication skills, attention to detail in preparing external presentations and performing data analysis.
- Understanding and proficiency of big data analysis and ability to translate these into visual representations.
- Strong written and verbal communication skills along with proven analytical aptitude.
- Team oriented with ability to effectively build relationships both externally and internally.

•	Creative thinking, ability to logically think through problems and present solutions to team members.